https://www.coloradotheatreguild.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyYou are here: Home1 / Privacy PolicyProtecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the
Colorado Theatre Producers Guild and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of
this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Colorado Theatre Producers Guild
include Colorado Theatre Guild and CTG. By using the CTG website, you consent to the data
practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally
sensitive data through CTG’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used
by others.
We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us.
However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to
use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an
account on our Site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners;
(c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e)
submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products
and services on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to,
communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We
also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Use of your Personal Information
CTG collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the
services you have requested.
CTG may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or
services available from CTG and its affiliates.
Sharing Information with Third Parties
CTG does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
CTG may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or
postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are
prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to CTG, and
they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
CTG may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in
the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or
comply with legal process served on CTG or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or
property of CTG; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of
users of CTG, or the public.
Tracking User Behavior
CTG may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within CTG, in order to determine
what CTG services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and
advertising within CTG to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a
particular subject area.
Automatically Collected Information
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by
CTG. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times
and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to
maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the CTG
website.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the
content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they
leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally
identifiable information.
Security of your Personal Information
CTG secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. CTG uses
the following methods for this purpose:
– SSL Protocol
When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is
protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.
We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or
alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or
any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to
protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy
limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and
privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site
cannot be guaranteed.
Children Under Thirteen
CTG does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age
of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for
permission to use this website.
E-mail Communications
From time to time, CTG may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements,
promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication. In order
to improve our Services, we may receive a notification when you open an email from CTG or
click on a link therein.
If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from
CTG, you may opt out of such communications by Clicking on the UNSUBSCRIBE button of
the email.
External Data Storage Sites
We may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have
contracted.
Changes to this Statement
CTG reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about
significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary
email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by
updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services
available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of
the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.
Contact Information
CTG welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe
that CTG has not adhered to this Statement, please contact CTG at:
Colorado Theatre Guild
P.O. Box 101866
Denver, Colorado 80250
Email Address:
Cotheatreguild@gmail.com
Telephone number:
720-739-0073
Effective as of January 1, 2020
CTG core statement Colorado Theatre Guild supports theatre production companies and artists in Colorado’s theatre communities, providing comprehensive resources, information, access and opportunities relating to live theatre events statewide.
Contact Information Colorado Theatre Guild
P.O. Box 101866
Denver, CO 80250
cotheatreguild@gmail.com
Support Theatre in Colorado See a Show
Become a Member
Jobs/Auditions
Connect With Us Facebook
